SPEAKER 1: Can I ask you to tell the story
SPEAKER 1: that you told about Bon Appetit magazine?
SPEAKER 2: I'm here to talk about you!
SPEAKER 1: So, the Bon Appetit magazine is in my new special,
SPEAKER 1 : the old man in the pool.
SPEAKER 1: No, it's a... Can you tell that story,
SPEAKER 1: or you don't want to tell it?
SPEAKER 2: Sure, I can tell it. I mean, it's a long story.
SPEAKER 2: We'll have to probably cut it out of the show.
SPEAKER 2: I don't know, but I was just telling this story that...
SPEAKER 1: I love this story.
SPEAKER 1: They cut it out, they cut it out.
SPEAKER 2: My mom was a very, very funny person,
SPEAKER 2: and she would call me up, and, like,
SPEAKER 2: she would say something to either annoy me
SPEAKER 2: or something like that, and I go,
SPEAKER 2: all right, Mom, I can't take it anymore.
SPEAKER 2: I got to hang up. She'd go, don't hang up.
SPEAKER 2: Wait, wait, one more thing. You know, whatever.